// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let que3 = [
    {
      numb: 1,
      question: "Javascript is an  Language?",
      answer: "Object-Oriented",
      options: [
        "Object-Oriented",
        "Object-Based",
        "Pocedural",
        "None of the Above"
      ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "How can a datatype be declared to be a constant type?",
        answer: "const",
        options: [
          "const",
          "var",
          "let",
          "constant"
        ]
      },
        
      {
        numb: 3,
        question: "Which object in JavaScript doesn't have a prototype?",
        answer: "Base Object",
        options: [
          "Base Object",
          "All objects have a prototype",
          "None of the objects have a prototype",
          "None of the Above"
        ]
      },
        
      
   
      {
      numb: 4,
      question: "Which of the following methods is used to access HTML elements using JavaScript?",
      answer: "Both A and B",
      options: [
        "getElementbyId()",
        "getElementsByClassName",
        "Both A and B",
        "None of the above"
      ]
    },
      {
        numb: 5,
        question: "Which of the following is not a JavaScript framework?",
        answer: "Cassandra",
        options: [
          "Node",
          "Vue",
          "React",
          "Cassandra"
        ]
      },
      {
        numb: 6,
        question: "Which of the following is not JavaScript Data Types?",
        answer: "Float",
        options: [
          "Undefined",
          " Number",
          "Boolean",
          "Float"
        ]
      },
      {
        numb: 7,
        question: "Which of the following method checks if its argument is not a number?",
        answer: "isNaN()",
        options: [
          "isNaN()",
          " nonNaN()",
          "NaN()",
          " None of the above"
        ]
      },
      {
        numb: 8,
        question: "Which of the following are the errors in JavaScript?",
        answer: "Run time errors",
        options: [
          "Load time errors",
          "Run time errors",
          "Logical Errors",
          "All of the above"
        ]
      },
      {
        numb: 9,
        question: "JavaScript ignores?",
        answer: "All of the above",
        options: [
          "spaces",
          "tabs",
          "newlines",
          "All of the above"
        ]
      },
      {
        numb: 10,
        question:  "Among the following, which one is a ternary operator in JavaScript?",
        answer: "?:",
        options: [
          "#",
          "::",
          "&:",
          "?:"
        ]
      }
      
  ];